[music]
>> Hello my tea babies. It's your girl
Tierra and you already know I'm back
with another video. I'm so excited
because I'm going out OF TOWN AGAIN.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> LET me calm down. But yeah, um this vlog
is going to consist of me getting my
maintenance done.
I have to get my nails and toes done
today. I got to get my eyebrows I mean
not eyebrows. My eyebrows are done. I
just got my eyebrows done. But I have to
get my lashes done.
Um today. Then I have to go shopping for
a little bit of stuff like I got to get
some
But yeah,
um
that and I have to go hygiene shopping
for the trip. Then tomorrow I get my
hair done and we leave and go out of
town.
If you know, you know, your girl never
stays in the city for too long. Like I
cannot stay in the city for that long.
So yeah, that's what this vlog will be
consisting of me prepping for my trip.
Me and Treasure is going to Tampa.
But yeah, we're going to Tampa. So um
I'm going to have two vlogs for y'all.
I'm going to have this vlog and then the
next vlog. I'm going to upload the next
vlog a couple of days after this one.
I'll give y'all time to like catch up on
all my videos. Um if you guys did not
watch the last video, the Q&A, please
stop this video go watch that. If you
didn't watch the other two videos,
Jamaica or what's the other one?
Orlando?
Go watch that.
Go watch those vlogs. Thank you.
I'm going to go get gas right now cuz
y'all know
your girl
gas is always empty.
So that's what I'm going to do. I don't
really like my eyebrows, but hopefully I
like, you know, when I get my lashes and
hair done I start liking it. Cuz right
now, I don't know. What y'all think?
Is my eyebrows good?
Y'all, I hate pumping my own gas like
This is just so unladylike. Like, why am
I pumping my own gas? Like, where's my
man?
I'm just a girl.
I'm feeling like a white man when I pump
my gas.
Baby, I am a N at heart. White N at
heart.
Cuz why am I pumping my gas?
Okay, so we're going to put it
a good $20 in my tank. That'll get me
from point A to point B
for these
next 2 days. Gas so high, y'all. Look.
Can y'all see that?
$3.90
freaking cent.
Y'all.
Oh, let me stop this.
But it take more than $20 on my tank. I
mean, on my car.
Oh, 20.
Y'all.
I just put $21 in my tank on accident.
It was supposed to be $20.
I needed my little dollar.
Ooh, y'all. It's so hot outside.
To the nail salon I go.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Okay, so the queen has arrived. Oh,
shoot.
I'm a little shorter.
So, I'm currently getting my nails done
first.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm getting cut down.
Because yeah.
I don't like them so long. I hate like
when they're
when it gets starts lifting, [music]
it starts hurting and stuff.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Here's the
finishing touch [music] on my nails.
Yes, they are cute.
>> [music]
>> Now I just got to get my toes done.
Y'all, me getting my toes done was way
overdue.
I think it's been a month.
>> [music]
>> I got them done. Last time I got them
done is when I went to Jamaica. So,
yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey y'all. So, I am out of Sunny Nails.
Um
I couldn't really show y'all how my toes
was looking because my camera was acting
stupid.
I don't know what be wrong with this
camera, but I'mma show y'all.
This is my nails and my toes.
So cute.
Y'all always get French too. Like this
is literally my go-to.
Wait, I kind of want some Tropical
Smoothie.
So, I think that's what I'm going to
eat.
Um
My phone on 9%, my camera on 15, so
I don't know which one I'm going to
charge first, but it might be my camera
cuz the camera charge fast. So, I guess
I'll talk to y'all when I get to the
food place.
Y'all at Tropical Smoothie.
Um can I have an apple?
And can I have a Bahama Mama smoothie?
Thank you.
I decided to get Tropical Smoothie.
I'm a little irked right now, but
cuz there's a lot going on, but I'll be
okay.
Y'all finna eat for a little bit, then
I'm finna go do the rest of my errands
then I have to run.
I'm not going to lie, I tore that
sandwich up. I couldn't even show y'all
what I got.
But I tore it up. I still got my
smoothie though.
Woo, y'all finally at the mall.
Okay, so oh, my first stop is literally
in my face.
Victoria's Secret. Am I the Am I the
that goes to Victoria Secret like every
time a trip is coming up? Like I have to
have a new pair of panties.
Like am I the only one that do that?
Literally every time I need a
five pair.
Oh, they got skims.
But
yeah.
Yeah, I'm I'm not that grown enough for
Victoria's Secret, so we're going to go
to Pink.
On the other side.
Cuz yeah.
I never ordered or anything from [music]
um Victoria's Secret. I always go to
Pink.
Hi. Oh, here we are.
Let's see if they have any deals today.
Five for 35. Thank you.
Perfect.
Um
what do I want to get?
I don't
So,
these are bikinis. I don't really like
bikini.
I don't want to get no thongs right now.
>> [music]
>> They do have some cute ones. I might get
like
I'm toxic. Ooh, perfect.
Y'all they have it in a small.
I think they have it in a small. I think
they have it in a small.
Perfect.
I'm toxic.
Y'all this is so cute.
So, I'm going to get these.
Um
I'm probably going to get these, then
the rest going to be like regular
panties. This the other [music] side,
y'all.
The pucker.
Boy shorts.
>> [music]
>> I kind of want some boy shorts. Um
>> I got these ones already.
That's [music] crazy.
Let's go to my size.
Small.
Okay, I don't have no black ones.
>> [music]
>> I guess I'm getting these black boy
shorts and then I want
some
I'll probably go to back to the bikini.
I might get a medium cuz look at how
they look.
Let me see how the medium look.
But I don't want it to be too tight.
>> [music]
>> Okay, I want cheeky.
This cheeky?
Okay, now this is perfect.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Is this medium?
I don't like the texture.
I'm so ready for Pink to um
to get the
the Halloween ones. Like they have some
Halloween ones, but I'm ready for the
ice.
>> [music]
>> These clothes.
Okay.
Her girlfriend.
I don't think I want this.
Her.
>> [music]
>> Okay, I don't have enough of that.
I'm just going to get
I got four. I'm just going to get one
more pair of thongs, y'all.
I be trying to try new new panties, but
baby, I like my thongs. I'm sorry.
I like my man
how I like my thongs.
Thank you.
Oh, these are cute.
I think I'm going to get these.
They do got these ones, too.
Halloween ones. I think I'm going to
just get this.
Okay, yeah.
So, I have what I want already.
Let's go to check out.
Okay, so I'm in the checkout line.
Um
I think I'm going to go hot girl
shopping tomorrow because
my lash appointment at 8:00 and it's
already 6:00 and I still
I still have to go home.
So, yeah.
I'm going to check out.
Thank you.
>> Take care.
>> Got my bag.
>> All right.
How are you?
>> Good.
>> All right, [music] y'all. So, next is
pick up my the stuff for my sister and
now I'm leaving this mall.
I'm not trying to spend nothing, y'all.
I'm going to spend so much money this
week.
I'm over it.
Oh, wow, I almost left De'Asia in the
store.
in the store, like
I'm about to leave.
I'm about to go home real quick.
I do need to pack, too, while I'm home,
but all I got to do is put all my stuff
in the suitcase
and I'm good.
>> [music]
>> Show me what you spend on me.
[music]
>> I'm so sad right now because my
tripod and stuff came, but guess what?
Y'all, it's the wrong tripod. I was
supposed to get the one that
has like I guess the charger piece in
it. I don't know, y'all. I'm just upset
right now.
Like I just spent my money on this for
no reason.
Hopefully I can order it to the Airbnb
that we're going to be at and it be here
cuz I really needed by Saturday.
Um but I got a case and stuff for my
um
camera until Haley buys my Hello Kitty
one.
But yeah.
I'm about to head to my lash
appointment. So I guess I'll talk to
y'all when I get there.
Okay, we finna go in.
Okay, y'all. So
I'm at my lash appointment. I'm getting
my lashes done and my hair done at the
same place. I get my hair done tomorrow
though
at 1:30.
And then your girl is going to Tampa.
This is April 4th. After I leave my um
lash appointment, I'm going to go to
Walmart.
So I'm going to get the rest of my stuff
that I need.
And yeah.
Yeah, why my lash tech forgot about me?
>> Child, I thought it was Wednesday.
I don't know why they want you to go so
short. They talking about some do I I
need to try wet wet a wet set or anime
that will bring out my No, I'm scared.
>> [laughter]
>> Not going to lie, I think anime might
eat on you.
>> Are you for real? How does it look?
Like y'all I'm trying to animate it.
>> [snorts]
>> I don't know who told me to do that but
thank you.
I'm about to try it.
And I think she's going to like it.
Y'all look a mess.
My eyes are already big so it look like
they popping out my head right now.
Y'all
I look crazy already.
>> [laughter]
>> So we putting down the spikes.
She nervous but I think this is really
going to be cute on her.
>> [singing]
[music]
[singing and music]
[music and singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> Okay everyone so I got my lashes done.
I was a little in a rush because it was
raining and stuff and I still have to go
to Walmart. So I'm going to show y'all
how it looks you know
in the light light when I get a chance
but yeah.
Y'all I tried anime so cute.
I get clusters. So yeah it's my girl DK
exotic clusters did them.
Y'all see the light in?
Let me focus on this road though. I'm on
the way to Walmart to get the rest of my
hygiene stuff for my trip.
I'm going to talk to y'all when I get
there.
Cuz it is raining bad.
And I cannot see at night and this is my
window fog in. So, yeah.
I'mma get with y'all later.
I'm finna go hygiene shopping.
Got to get the rest of my stuff before
my trip.
I got to get a buggy.
Need one of these.
Y'all see the water?
Oh my gosh, this buggy is so wet.
I think it'll be okay though.
Y'all, I like to go down every aisle
first.
So, I make to make sure like I'm not
going to be missing out on anything.
So,
how much is
this perhaps?
Me and Treasure be using this for our
face.
Um
cuz I don't think I have any more, so
they got a small bottle.
But, I don't need no 91%.
I think I'mma get the 50%.
So, I'mma get this.
What is this?
Are these wipes? Oh, these medical
wipes.
I don't got no hemorrhoids, so I don't
know why I'm
um
looking at that.
Let's go.
Okay, y'all. So,
my favorite section,
travel stuff.
Um
I got most of this stuff already.
I
just need some soap.
I probably get another one of these, but
I got so many of them.
I want these.
500, 10 of them.
I think I'mma get these just because.
This is extra hold spray.
Should I get this?
Think I'mma get this, too.
And I need some mousse.
Oh, I need [music] some
this.
This what I got so far, y'all.
I always get a new toothbrush, [music]
too.
I don't know why I do that, but every
time but this got the whole kit. So,
maybe I'll just get the kit. [music]
I already have deodorant.
But, I mean I can use a little travel
deodorant.
Like that.
I do I get a hairbrush, too.
So.
I'm trying to see if I want to get these
ones
or
these are the smaller ones. I think I'm
just get the smaller ones.
I heard that these are very good
for you.
I want to try them. If you guys ever
tried this, let me know how it is and
I'll probably come back and get this.
But, I heard it's good. This my cart so
far.
I just got to get some [music] soap.
I'm trying to make sure I'm not missing
anything else. Um,
I stay losing my brushes. Like I don't
know what I be doing with my brushes.
But, I'm going to get a brush.
I think I'm going to get this.
Okay.
I do need some mousse.
So, let's see what they got.
Um.
Do I need anything from up here, y'all?
I think I'm good.
>> [music]
>> Let me get this, too.
Let me get
some makeup wipes then I'm leaving. I
mean,
>> [music]
>> and some soap then I'm leaving.
They might have some down the other
aisle.
Why don't I see the soap?
They don't want me to wash my ass.
Oh, you got the soap right here.
I get Dove soap.
One should be enough for 3 days.
Um
and
I got to go back to the travel aisle.
Was it down here?
>> [music]
>> Yeah, it was down here.
Oh, they sure do.
$1.
Thank you.
I already got some lotion.
I don't need that.
I think I'm good.
I'm finished. I don't know if I showed
y'all everything I got, but I'm going to
show y'all now.
So,
this is all the stuff I got.
The rest of the stuff is home already.
This is just the extra stuff that I got
to get.
But, some of this stuff I don't even
really need to get. So, I'm going to
just sort out stuff that I really need
and stuff that I like I can go without
cuz I already have
those little
white sponge I mean those blue that blue
and grey sponge already.
I got deodorant already, but I just want
extra. I don't know why I'm like that.
So, yeah.
I wish I had my tripod.
Ah.
I don't need that.
Ooh.
I don't need that white.
I do need this for sure.
We'll put that on there.
I'm at $14, y'all.
That can hold off real quick. Definitely
need that.
Hold spray, $17.
I'm just going to get all this. I don't
even care no more.
This my total.
This everything I got.
I end up getting everything, so ooh. Oh
lord, what am I doing?
Ha, I didn't mean to do that.
>> There you go.
>> Wait, I didn't want it to remove.
>> You didn't want it removed?
>> No.
I don't even know. I don't even know.
Thank you.
Okay, y'all.
So, I'm about to pay.
Pay.
Pay now.
>> You're all set, Tiara.
>> Now, I'm about to go home.
My mama cooked some spaghetti, so yes.
I'm so excited.
All right, let me get my stuff and let's
go.
I did everything I said I was going to
do today.
So, tomorrow I just got to get my hair
done. I got to wake up early in the
morning though to get a oil change for
this rental.
But, we going to be on the hot of road
somewhere, so.
That's all I'm doing tomorrow.
I'm going to go pack.
And yeah.
I'll talk to y'all tomorrow. Good
morning, T babies.
It's the next day. Um, and right now I
am currently getting a oil change for my
rental.
Because we going to hit that road later,
so yeah.
Got to make sure my car is good and the
car will make it to Tampa.
Cuz it's very is very very very very
very late on the oil change.
Okay y'all, so I made it to my hair
appointment. I couldn't even give y'all
an update cuz I was rushing here.
I thought I was going to be late, but
I'm here.
T babies, why is he playing with y'all?
You want to shout yourself out.
>> You want to shout yourself out?
>> Shout yourself out.
>> You know, it's Jay Antoine in it open
the window.
>> Thank you.
>> Y'all can see the open the window.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thank you.
I'mma put his um Instagram
in my description [music]
for y'all.
>> [music]
[music]
>> This week is from Jayonte, the one who
do my hair.
>> Period.
>> Y'all got to over here. Oh my god.
>> There ain't no bed over here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I love me a good Florida install.
I wouldn't know what to do if I was from
another state, boy.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, my tea babies. That is all for
this vlog.
Um, I got everything done. Cute cute
hair team.
I hope you guys enjoy this vlog. Please
make sure you guys like, comment, and
share. Don't forget to follow me or
subscribe to my channel.
I hope you guys enjoyed this video.
And if you guys want to see more, don't
forget to subscribe.
See you later T babies.